wcm7.com 2014-03-31

# WCM 7

[ Last Modified: December 17, 2012 ]  
Information we collect  
We collect information to provide better services to all of our users – from figuring out basic stuff like which language you speak, to more complex things like which ads you’ll find most useful or the people who matter most to you online.  
We collect information in two ways:  
Information you give us. For example, many of our services require you to sign up an account. When you do, we’ll ask for personal information, like your name, email address, telephone number or credit card.   
Information we get from your use of our services. We may collect information about the services that you use and how you use them, like when you visit a website that uses our advertising services or you view and interact with our ads and content. This information includes:  
Device information  
We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information including phone number).   
Log information  
When you use our services or view content provided by us, we may automatically collect and store certain information in service logs. This may include:  
●details of how you used our service, such as your search queries.  
●IP address.  
●device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL.  
●cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.  
Location information  
When you use a location-enabled service, we may collect and process information about your actual location, like GPS signals sent by a mobile device. We may also use various technologies to determine location, such as sensor data from your device that may, for example, provide information on nearby Wi-Fi access points and cell towers.  
Unique application numbers  
Certain services include a unique application number. This number and information about your installation (for example, the operating system type and application version number) may be sent to us when you install or uninstall that service or when that service periodically contacts our servers, such as for automatic updates.  
Local storage  
We may collect and store information (including personal information) locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5) and application data caches.  
Cookies and anonymous identifiers  
We use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit our service, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anomymous identifiers to your device. We also use cookies and anonymous identifiers when you interact with services we offer to our partners.  
How we use information we collect  
We use the information we collect from all of our services to provide, maintain, protect and improve them, to develop new ones, and to protect us and our users. We also use this information to offer you tailored content – like giving you more relevant search results and ads.  
We may use the name you provide for your account Profile across all of the services we offer. In addition, we may replace past names associated with your account so that you are represented consistently across all our services. If other users already have your email, or other information that identifies you, we may show them your publicly visible profile information, such as your name and photo.  
When you contact us, we may keep a record of your communication to help solve any issues you might be facing. We may use your email address to inform you about our services, such as letting you know about upcoming changes or improvements.  
We use information collected from cookies and other technologies to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our services. For example, by saving your language preferences, we’ll be able to have our services appear in the language you prefer. When showing you tailored ads, we will not associate a cookie or anonymous identifier with sensitive categories, such as those based on race, religion, sexual orientation or health.  
We may combine personal information from one service with information, including personal information, from other services – for example to make it easier to share things with people you know. We will not combine DoubleClick cookie information with personally identifiable information unless we have your opt-in consent.  
We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those that are set out in this Privacy Policy.  
We process personal information on our servers in many countries around the world. We may process your personal information on a server located outside the country where you live.  
Transparency and choice  
People have different privacy concerns. Our goal is to be clear about what information we collect, so that you can make meaningful choices about how it is used.   
You may also set your browser to block all cookies, including cookies associated with our services, or to indicate when a cookie is being set by us. However, it’s important to remember that many of our services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.   
Information you share  
Many of our services let you share information with others. Remember that when you share information publicly, it may be indexable by search engines. Our services provide you with different options on sharing and removing your content.  
Accessing and updating your personal information  
Whenever you use our services, we aim to provide you with access to your personal information. If that information is wrong, we strive to give you ways to update it quickly or to delete it – unless we have to keep that information for legitimate business or legal purposes. When updating your personal information, we may ask you to verify your identity before we can act on your request.  
We may reject requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort (for example, developing a new system or fundamentally changing an existing practice), risk the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes).  
Where we can provide information access and correction, we will do so for free, except where it would require a disproportionate effort. We aim to maintain our services in a manner that protects information from accidental or malicious destruction. Because of this, after you delete information from our services, we may not immediately delete residual copies from our active servers and may not remove information from our backup systems.  
Information we share  
We do not share personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of WCM unless one of the following circumstances apply:  
With your consent  
We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of WCM when we have your consent to do so.   
For external processing  
We provide personal information to our affiliates or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.  
For legal reasons  
We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of WCM if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:  
○meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.  
○enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.  
○detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.  
○protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Google, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.  
We may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information publicly and with our partners – like publishers, advertisers or connected sites.   
If WCM is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, we will continue to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information and give affected users notice before personal information is transferred or becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  
Information security  
We work hard to protect WCM and our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold.  
Application  
Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by WCM and its affiliates, including services offered on other sites, but excludes services that have separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this Privacy Policy.  
Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you in search results, sites that may include our services, or other sites linked from our services.   
Enforcement  
We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.  
Changes  
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes).
